Guide to the J.J. Donovan Papers 1872-1941
Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Published Materials, 1894-1937; Series VIII
  - Northern Pacific Railway Company - Engineering Rules and Instructions, 1889 (Box M2, Folder 6)
  - Pacific Highway by-laws pamphlet, undated (Box M2, Folder 7)
  - Assorted pamphlets, 1901-1904 (Box M2, Folder 8-10)
  - Political flyers, undated (Box M2, Folder 11)
  - Pocket Dictionary with notation "A Souvenir of the SNS, given by Prof. H.O. Ladd", 1876 (Box M2, Folder 12)
  - Statement on prostitution by J.J. Donovan in the Bellingham Herald, 1910 (Box M2, Folder 13)
  - Religious publications, undated (Box M2, Folder 14)
  - Life's Handicap by Rudyard Kipling, 1912 (Box M2, Folder 15)
  - Speech of the Hon. William E. Humphrey, House of Representatives, 1908 May 18 (Box M2, Folder 16)
  - Theater playbills, circa 1930s (Box M2, Folder 17)
  - Travel brochures and maps, 1924-1925 (Box M2, Folder 18)
  - Whatcom County Auditor's Report, 1895 (Box M2, Folder 19)
  - Birch Bark Poems by Charles F. Lummis, 1882 (Box M2, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers re: J.J. Donovan, undated (Box M3)
  - State of Washington Governor's Proclamation of Thankgiving Day, 1906 (Oversize-box M4/1)